Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files 5623
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files
1930-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT)
5623
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Records (documents), correspondence, case files.
Arbitration case files, correspondence, monthly reports and state legislation reports.
5677080
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 09, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen was founded in 1883 in Oneonta, N.Y. as a protective and insurance organization. By the time of its merger with three other railroad labor unions to form the United Transportation Union in 1969, it had the greatest membership of any of the operating railroad brotherhoods.
The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT) was established to represent members' interests in obtaining a satisfactory contract with management. The first Canadian lodge was established in Moncton, New Brunswick in 1885, and the first Ladies' Auxiliary was organized in Fort Gratiot, Mich. in 1889. These records reflect the union's political and fraternal activities as well as its actions in the areas of collective bargaining, grievances, and railroad and labor legislation. As the largest of the unions which merged to form the United Transportation Union in 1969, the bulk of its then current files formed the basis for the files now held in the merged union's headquarters.
The rail service members of the BRT included conductors and their assistants, dining car stewards, ticket collectors, train baggagemen, brakemen, and train flagmen. The yard service members of the BRT included yardmasters, yard conductors, switchtenders, foremen, flagmen, brakemen, switchmen, car tenders, operators, hump riders, and car operators. In 1933, the BRT organized interstate bus operators, and included them under BRT contracts held with U.S. bus companies.
BRT officers were elected at the Grand Lodge Convention of the Brotherhood, held every 4 years. The principal officers included a president, an assistant to the president, a general secretary-treasurer, Canadian and national legislative representatives, a senior vice-president, BRT representative, and National Railroad Board of Adjustment representative. The BRT had four governing boards: the Board of Directors, Board of Trustees and Insurance, Board of Appeals, and Executive Board.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5021: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Records 5102: Emergency Board No. 129, Long Island Railroad and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locals 517 and 1090, Records 5149: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149 MB: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia 5149 P: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 5348: W.P. Kennedy as President of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen against the Long Island Railroad Company Court Documents 5446: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Ledger 5612: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Moosic Tunnel Lodge no.93 Meeting Minutes 5631: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad General Committee File 5647: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Joppa Lodge (Toledo, OH) Minute Books 5894: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Railroad Booklets 6268 P: Joint Committee of Adjustment for the Rock Island System's Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photograph 6312 P: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 6312 PUBS: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Publications 6312m: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Annual Report of the Legislative Board 6405 PUBS: William Sharp Collection of The Railroad Trainmen's Journal 6480 MB: Paul Berger Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia
Cabooses (Railroads); Collective labor agreements -- Railroads -- United States; Transport workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Political activity; AFL-CIO; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen (U.S.); Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen (U.S.) Legislative Board of New York.; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Erie Railroad Company; Long Island Rail Road; New York City Railway Company
5677080
- State of New York. Public Services Commission - Discontuance and Complaint Case Files, PSC Cases 1341-22918 (Box 1)
  - PSC Case 1341 - NY Central - Hudson Riv. RRs - re "bridge ticklers" in elec. Zone (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - PSC 2950 - Petition EL Dorsey for operation bus line Binghamton - Corbettsville (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - PSC 5688 - Petition PRR re temporary suspension trains 9305 - 9310 Buffalo - Olean. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - PSC 6830 - Complaint J. Fitzgibbons vs USRR Adm. And NYCRR (Walkill Valley) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - PSC 6935 - J. Fitzgibbons vs. US RR Adm - NYCRR - re operation without baggage man (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - PSC 6865 - In re US RR Adm. - B&MRR in re employees being towed (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - PSC 7134 - Martin Degnan, CGGC D&H re 54-a in operation of passenger trains (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PSC 7189 - Triple Cities Trac. Co. for authority operate buses in lieu of rails (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - PSC 7323 - J. Fitzgibbons vs. C NE Ry re violation 54 -a Railroad law (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PSC 7487 - NY Central RR - application for authority to discontinue train 705Alb-Troy (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - PSC 7643 - T.E. Ryan, Leg. Chairman BLF&E vs. Buffalo, Rochester, Pittsburgh Ry - 54-a (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - PSC 7504 - NY Central RR - discontinuance trains Dresden - PennYan. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - PSC 8248 - D&H RR - in re operations certain trains violated 54 - a Ft. Edward Br. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - PSC 9381- Proceedings in re employees working on riding on top of trains (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - PSC 10050 - Complaint BRT vs. D&H RR- facilities at Tub Mt. (Whitehall) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - PSC 10283 - In re service by Lehigh Valley Canastota to Ithaca, New York (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - PSC 10588 - In re service by DL&W RR between Owego and Ithaca (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - PSC 10596 - In re service by Erie RR between Dunkirk and Salamanca (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - PSC 10599 - In re service by NYC RR between Syracuse and Richland via Owego (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - PSC 11691 - BRT-BLE-BLF&E vs. DL&W RR in re certain efficiency tests (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - PSC 11971 - In re complaint certain commuters re service by Erie Buffalo-Hornell (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - PSC 12240 - NYO&W - petition to discontinue 1-2, 12-37, Cornwall - Walton, NY (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - PSC 12292 - Drinking water at Selkirk (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - PSC 10617 - In re service by NYC RR between Kingston and Albany - River Division (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - PSC 10636 - In re service by DL&W RR between Pa. - N.Y. line and Buffalo (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - PSC 10795 - In re practice of D&H RR in operation and maintenance Harpursville tunnel (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - PSC 11346 - Motor Bus Rules and Regulations (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - PSC 11660 - In re equipment, appliances, and facility at intersection of sidings, etc. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - PSC 12531 - In re service by NYC RR Syracuse to Albany and intermediate pts. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - PSC 13131 - Ch. Of Commerce complaint against service curtailment Utica-Oswego (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - SC 13200 - Erie RR - petition to discontinue trains 467-468 Avon-Corning, N.Y. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - PSC 13209 - Lodge 311 vs. B&MRR - unsafe conditions - violation 54 -b &c (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - PSC 13276 - PRR - discontinuance trains - 990-991 Buffalo to Olean (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - PSC 13318 - NYC RR (B&A Div.) - Full Crew law applicability (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - PSC 13591 - Lehigh Valley RR - discontinuance trains 301-302 Ithaca to Auburn (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - PSC 13647 - customers vs. Lehigh Valley RR re trains 282-283 - Sayre Auburn Div. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - PSC 13733 - Oswego Ch. Of Commerce vs. DL&W RR curtailment of service Syracuse Oswego (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - PSC 13894 - Lodge 556 vs. PRR re 54-a light locomotives Buffalo - Ebeneze (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - PSC 13760 - Village Sherburne vs. DL&WRR in re trains 1803-1806 Binghamton-Utica (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - PSC 13932 - Lodge 244 vs. NYC RR -54-c transfer-switching cabooses E. Buffalo (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - PSC 13934 - Lodge 560 re change in rates affect RR employees Staten Island Railway & Rapid Transit Ry (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - PSC 13944 - Ch. Comm. Auburn, Seneca Falls, Waterloo vs. NYC RR discontinuance trains 5-12 Syracuse-Geneva (Box 1, Folder 42)
- State of New York. Public Services Commission - Discontuance and Complaint Case Files, PSC Cases 1341-22918 (Box 2)
  - PSC 13945 - Lodge 681 vs. NYC RR discontinuance 42-49 Rochester-Suspension Br. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - PSC 13946 - Lodges 164-480 vs. NYC RR discontinuance trains 7 - 1 - 1-, St. Lawrence Div. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - PSC 13970 - Ch. Comm. - Salamanca and Ellicottville vs. B&O discontinuance trains 60-61 E. Salamanca - Buffalo(also L.137) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - PSC 14076 - In re proposed discontinuance and inquiry into service West Shore NYCR (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - PSC 14076-14132 - West Shore NYCRR inquiry into service and proposed discontinuance (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - PSC 14317 - Lodge 220 vs. Erie RR - proposed discontinuance train 471 - Attica Buffalo (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - PSC 14326 - Lodge 639 - City N. Falls - discontinuance trains Buff. Susp. Bridge (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - PSC 14361 - D&H RR - discontinuance Sara. -N. Creek 9/30-5/15-L90,296,311 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PSC 14368 - PRR proposed discontinuance 594-597 Canandaigua -NY Pa St. Line (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - PSC 14523 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 13,25,16,26 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - PSC 14524 - NYCRR - proposed discontinuance 67-72 Utica-Watertown (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PSC 14531 - Bd Supers. Westchester City. Vs. NYC RR re discontinuance trains Putnam Div. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - PSC 14527 - NYC RR - Lodge 164 - proposed discontinuance DeKalb - Ogdensburg (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - PSC 14650 - Lodge 289 - Ellicottville Ch. Comm. Re discontinuance trains 852-853 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - PSC 14674 - Lodge 517 et al. vs. Long Island RR re discontinuance trains east of Patchogue (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - PSC 14679 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 97 W. Haverstraw - Newburgh (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - PSC 14697 - Long Island RR - proposed discontinuance trains - Main Line Branch (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - PSC 14805-15099 - DL&W - NYC RR - NYO&WRR - elimination crossing watch - men - installing flashing lights (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - PSC 14817 - Long Island RR - withdrawal trains Wading River Branch (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - PSC 14818 - Erie RR - discontinuance trains 61-64 - Port Jervis - Suffern (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - PSC 14819 - D&H RR-restoration trains 202-209 Binghamton-Albany (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - PSC 15109 - Erie RR - proposed discontinuance trains 477-478 Buffalo-Hornell (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - PSC 15157 - Long Island RR - proceeding re regulations, etc., in transportation of passengers in State of New York (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 15316 - Oswego vs. NYC RR - trains 336-337 - Syracuse and Oswego (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 15325 - B&O RR - proposed discontinuance trains 67-68 - Perry and Rochester (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 15433 - Long Island RR - elimination 11 trains between Jamaica ad NY City (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - PSC 15545-15573 - NYC RR re discontinuance trains 6-19, 20-25, Albany-Weehawken - Albany-Kingston, West Shore (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 15611 - Long Island RR - change in schedules and discontinuance certain trains between Jamaica and Greenport (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 15631 - D&H RR - proposed discontinuance 16014 #5 between Whitehall - Plattsburgh (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - PSC 15704 - D&H RR - proposed discontinuance 181-182 - Sara. Springs. N. Creek (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - PSC 15852 - Staten Island RR - elimination all passenger service S.I.R.T. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - PSC 16116 - Erie RR - proposed discontinuance trains 27-28 1 Pt. Jervis-Binghamton (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - PSC 16168 - NYC RR - elimination train37 Weehawken-Ravena; 527-528 Catskill Mt. Branch (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - PSC 16183 NYC RR(B&A) discontinuance trains between Chatham and NY-Mass line Albany-NY-Mass line (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - PSC 16214 - PRR - discontinuance trains 570-571 Buffalo-Harrisburg (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - PSC 16241 - B&O RR - proposed discontinuance 851-852 - Rochester- E. Salamanca (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - PSC 16319 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 6 Putnam Div. Trains (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - PSC 16415 - Rutland RR - PS investigation discontinuance certain trains (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - PSC 16447 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 40-49 between Westfield-NY City (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - PSC 16542 - Dispute on transfer of franchise to Albany-Schenectady bus line (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - PSC 17160 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue passenger service River Division (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - PSC 17167 - D&H RR - petition to discontinue all passenger service Saratoga Springs to North Creek (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - PSC 17251 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue 42-49 - Rochester Susp. Bridge (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - PSC 17304 - B&O RR - proposed discontinuance 251-252 Buffalo Pittsburgh (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - PSC 17410 - D&H RR - proposed discontinuance 3-4, 40-41, 7-8, Whall to Rouses Pt. 34 Saratoga Springs -Troy (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - PSC 17411 - PRR - discontinuance trains 595-596-598 Canandaigua-Williamsport Pa. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - PSC 17451 - D&H RR - authority to operate Laurentian via Albany (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - PSC 17476 - Rockland Transit Corp. authority to operate Nyack-Tarrytown (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - PSC 17773 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance holiday trains 621-624- Albany Mass. Line (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - PSC 17801 - Complaint Lodge 823 vs. New Haven RR - Van Nest Switcher (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - PSC 17904 - NYC RR - Lodge 480 complaint re proposed discontinuance 11 St. Lawrence Div. trains (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - PSC 17992 - D&H RR - proposed discontinuance 3-4-14 - Whitehall -Albany (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - PSC 18033 - NYC RR - proposed elimination all service Putnam Div. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - PSC 18114 - Complaint BRT re adoption of close clearance rules St. of NY (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - PSC 18278 - D&H RR - petition to discontinue all passenger trains Saratoga - N. Creek (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - PSC18440 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 42-49 - Suspension Bridge Rochester (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - PSC 18519 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 3,7,8,18 Syracuse - Rochester (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - PSC 18520 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 4-5 between Lake Clear Jct-Malone (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - PSC 18559 - NYC - petition to discontinue train 706 - Troy to Albany (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - PSC 18560 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance 146 - Troy, NY City (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - PSC 18561 - B&M RR - proposed discontinuance 12 trains VT-NY Line to Troy (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - PSC 18761 - NYC RR proposed discontinuance 94-96-95 Buffalo Albany - NY City (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - PSC 18798 - D&H RR petition for authority to discontinue trains 2-5 north of Whall (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - PSC 18942 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue all service St. Lawrence Division (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - PSC 19198 - Lodge 823 vs. NY NH & H RR alleged violation 54 - a on main line (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - PSC 19415 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue trains Rochester -Suspension Bridge (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - PSC 19472 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue all passenger ser. Utica-Lake Placid (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - PSC 19549 - Erie RR - petition to discontinue 55-60-78 Pt. Jervis Pa NY Line (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - PSC 21101 - D&H RR - petition to discontinue 3-4-14 between Whitehall-Albany (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - PSC 21217-21219-NYC RR-petition to eliminate Hudson Station (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - PSC 21367 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue 901-901-908 NY City-Chatham (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - PSC 21437 - NYC - petition to discontinue 118,119,120,121 Susp. Br. And Buffalo (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - PSC 21542 - NYC RR - petition for authority to eliminate all passenger service (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - PSC 21543 - NYC RR - petition to discontinue all pass. Ser. St. Lawrence Div. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - PSC 21573 - Long Island RR - application for combination rail-bus ser. Greenport NY City (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - PSC 21699 - NYC RR - application. To discontinue 495-496 - Chatham to Albany (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - PSC 22213 - D&H RR petition to discontinue 4-5 Saratoga Albany and return (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - PSC 22392 - D&H RR - petition discontinuance 205-208 - Albany - Binghamton (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - PSC 22498 - E-L RR - petition to discontinue 193-194 Syracuse and Massena (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - PSC 22918 - NYC RR - proposed discontinuance #2 between Buffalo and Albany (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Industrial Safety Rule Violations Case Files C99-813 - C99-955 (Box 3)
  - C-99-614 Erie-Lackawanna Cabooses - File #4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - C-99-614 Erie-Lackawanna Cabooses File #5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - C-99-614 - Erie-Lackawanna Cabooses (Code 42 Violations) File #1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - C-99-813 L-1440 Unsanitary St. Geo. Terminal, Staten Island RR, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Scope and Contents
    November 30, 1967
  - C-99-848 Code 42 B7O RR Rochester N.Y. Cabooses, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    May 3, 1968
  - C-99-840 Code 42 B&O RR Springville, N.Y., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    August 20, 1968
  - C-99-838 L-346 Code 42 E-L RR Elmira, N.Y. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    September 27, 1968
  - C-99-834 L-1530 E-L Hamburg, NY Unsanitary Conditions (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - C-99-831 - Bus Lodges - NJ Board - request for removal of restrictions on charter buses (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - C-99-829 L-1530 Alleged Code 42 violations at Gowanda, E-L RR (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - C-99-822 Code 42 Silver Springs Depot E-L RR, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - C-99-820 L-735 Code 42 Violations Brooks Ave, Roch NY B&O RR, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    February 22, 1968
  - C-99-807 L-377 Unsafe & Unsanitary E-L RR Salamanca, Jamestown, NY, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    September 1967
  - C-99-804 L-1007 E-L RR Unsafe & Unsanitary Syracuse, Utica, NY, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - C-99-614 - Erie - Lackawanna Cabooses File No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - C-99-935 L1430 - Caboose Complaints E-L Railway (Lackawanna side) Code Rule 42 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - C-99-930 - L#1566 - Caboose complaints, Buffalo, New York (Box 3, Folder 17)
    March 27, 1972
  - C-99-927 - L#326 - Violations of the Caboose Law E-L Railway between Elmira & Hornell, N.Y. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    December 29, 1971
  - C-99-926 - L735 - Bunkroom, Lincoln Park, Rochester, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    November 9, 1971
  - C-99-915 L-1491 E-L RR Unsanitary conditions Newburgh, NY (Box 3, Folder 20)
    June 7, 1970
  - C-99-909 L-1430 E-L RR Buffalo, NY Unsanitary Conditions, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    January 29, 1970
  - C-99-906 L-377 E-L RR Unsanitary facilities Salamanca, NY, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    December 8, 1969
  - C-99-904 L-301 E-L RR Unsanitary facilities Norwich, NY, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    November 20, 1969
  - C-99-900 L-735 Locker Room Situation, Leroy N.Y., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    October 29, 1969
  - C-99-897 L-1530 & L-1566 E-L RR Buff., NY unsanitary conditions (Box 3, Folder 25)
    September 11, 1969
  - C-99-896 L-319 LV RR & B&O RR Niagara Falls & Buff, NY Unsanitary conditions (Box 3, Folder 26)
    September 15, 1969
  - C-99-891 L-1968 Unsanitary conditions E-L RR Syracuse, NY - facilities & cabooses, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    July, 18, 1969
  - C-99-887 L-377 B&O RR Salamanca, NY Unsanitary facilities, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    June 9, 1969
  - C-99-884 L-346 NYS Dept. Health unsanitary drinking water Gang Mills NY, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    May 7, 1969
  - C-99-880 L-1491 Unsanitary Cond's Yd. Employees Port Jervis E-L (Box 3, Folder 30)
    March 6, 1969
  - C-99-864 L-1530 & L-1430 Unsanitary Bunkrm. E-L Rochester, NY (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - C-99-863 L-1491 Unsanitary Locker - Lunch Rm. Middletown, NY (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - C-99-862 L-318 Caboose Complaints Hornell, NY, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    November 21, 1968
  - C-99-941 - L#346 - Unsanitary working conditions - Gang Mills Yd. - Elmira, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - C-99-943 - L1491 - Erie Lackawanna Fumes emitted from toilets on locomotive (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - C-99-944 - L1430 - E-L Railway "T Cabooses" - Caboose T-26 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - C-99-945 - L735 Transporting employee by cab., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    April 23, 1973
  - C-99-947 L#1530 Unsanit. Cabooses (Box 3, Folder 38)
    January 1, 1974
  - C-99-949 # 318 - Unsanity conditions Hornell, NY - Shelter & Locker Room, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    June 24, 1974
  - C-99-950 #1726 - E-L & N&W RR Bison Yard Locker Room, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    June 25, 1974
  - C-99-952 #1968 - EL Railway Co. Engine house & Facilities - Utica, NY unsanitary condition - July 19, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - C-99-954 - E-L - #346 - Unsanitary conditions Elmira and Gang Mills Lunchroom Elmira, NY, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    August, 5, 1974`
  - C-99-955 L#318 E-L Unsanitary Conditions on Engines, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    October 29, 1974
  - C-99-844 L-211 Code 42 E-L RR Binghamton, NY (Box 3, Folder 44)
    October 18, 1968
- General Committee Files (alphabetical by railroad) (Box 4)
  - General Committee - Boston & Maine RR (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - General Committee - Boston & Albany RR (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Albany Port District Commission Railroad (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - General Committee - NKP RR (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - General Committee - New Haven RR (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - General Committee P-C Lines West (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - International Assn of Gen. Chairmen (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Vermont Railway (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General Comm. - New York Central-East (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General Committee - Long Island RR (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General Committee - Erie RR (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - General Comm - Pennsylvania RR (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - General Committee - Delaware & Hudson (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Information - NYC RR - passenger service (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Subject Files - A-C (Box 5)
  - AFL-CIO (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO State Convention - 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO News Bulletins (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Application New York Trainmen's Ass'n Inc. Before Board of Standards & Appeals for Certif. of Inc. or Charter (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Applications of Riss & Company, MC-200 & Consolidated Cases, MC-35628, Interstate Motor Freight System, et al., for authority to transport dangerous explosives over the highways and city streets in the United States (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Association of Railroads of New York (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1960 - Bills and Statements (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bills and Statements - 1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bus Department 1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bus Department 1960 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bus Department - 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bus Department (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Caboose Cupolas - 1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - AL H. Chesser, Nat'l Leg. Rep., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 16)